{
    "subject": "resource/Subhumans_(Canadian_band)",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "resource/British_Columbia",
    "human_readable": "Subhumans (Canadian band) originated from British Columbia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9363327622413635,
            "question": "Where did the Canadian band Subhumans originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8964636325836182,
            "question": "Is Subhumans a Canadian band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8151167631149292,
            "question": "What is the origin province of the band Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6102192997932434,
            "question": "What is the history of the band Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5261907577514648,
            "question": "In which region did Subhumans form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4091030955314636,
            "question": "Is there any information about the members of Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3632065951824188,
            "question": "What is known about the musical genre of Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2889992296695709,
            "question": "Has Subhumans toured internationally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25010955333709717,
            "question": "What are some notable songs by Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20017915964126587,
            "question": "Are there any famous albums by Subhumans?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Subhumans (Canadian band) originated from British Columbia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1699_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable songs by Subhumans?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1699_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Subhumans toured internationally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1699_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about the musical genre of Subhumans?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1699_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1699_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that it supports the triple. Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided confirms that the Canadian punk band \"Subhumans\" was formed in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1699/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Subhumans (Canadian band) originated from British Columbia.\" Multiple documents specify that the band formed in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}